## RUEI-PU(ALLEN) KOU

17 Cawker Ct, Whitby, ON 905-966-3228 <u>www.AllenKou.info</u> <u>imakou@gmail.com</u>

#### **PROFILE**

Front End developer with 4+ years of experience in the industry and solid knowledge of HTML, CSS, JS and frameworks including **React.js** / **Redux**, **Bootstrap** and **Material UI**. Extensive experiences with using **Git**, **Docker**, **Webpack** and **Babel** (ES6/7). Completed multiple CMS and personal side-projects. More show cases on <u>www.AllenKou.info</u>

#### **SKILLS**

Javascript. ReactJS. Redux. HTML. CSS (SASS). Node.JS. Express. GraphQL. MongoDB. React Native. Git. Docker. Mocha. Ant Design. Materail UI. Bootstrap. Chromeless. RWD. Selenium. AWS.

#### **EDUCATION**

Diploma in Computer Programmer Seneca College Toronto, ON,Canada | 2015.01 – 2015.07 Bachelor in Information management Hsing-Wu University Taipei, Taiwan | 2007.08 – 2011.08

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### WEB DEVELOPER - GELENK NETWORK INC | MARKHAM, ON, CANADA | 2018.09 - PRESENT

- Developed web message APP with feature including Realtime SMS or MMS sending and receiving, user-friendly UI implemented by Material UI, drafts auto-save, and built-in message templates using React and Redux.
- Develop a telephone configuration CMS named GenVoice Portal wth features including pie charts and graph usage visualization by BizChart, bills expiration as formatted PDF files, and a IVR (Interactive Voice Response) system with a visual keypad using React and Redux.
- Provided React and Redux training to new staff
- Deploy production and develop environment by Docker-Compose
- Work collaboratively with a team of back end developer, system architect and project manager.

# FRONT END DEVELOPER - UNIVERSITY OF WATERLOO - CONRAD BUSINESS CENTRE WATERLOO, ON, CANADA | 2017.05 - 2017.09

- Implemented features based on React and Redux
- Practiced features including dynamic data graph, real-time chatting (Twilio's API)
- Built BDD testing practices (e2e by Cucumber, Selenium and Mocha)
- Cooperated with UI/UX team and enhanced website's components to be more user friendly

#### WEB DEVELOPER - DIGIM | TAIPEI, TAIWAN | 2014.01 - 2014.05

- Developed retina display friendly RWD pages
- Collaborated with the creative and back-end teams
- Provide Sass and HTML template(ERB) training to colleagues

## WEB DEVELOPER - REXHOLIDAY | TAIPEI, TAIWAN | 2013.07 - 2013.12

- Collaborated with stakeholders to improve an internal itinerary system
- Developed internal IT devices plan
- Enhanced colleagues' workflow using SaaS

### WEB DEVELOPER - WEBIKE.TW | TAIPEI, TAIWAN | 2013.01 - 2013.06

- Designed and developed the first version prototype of eCommerce website base on Magneto
- Organized over 300k primitive data to MySQL database
- Deployed project to EC2 instances in LAMP environment on AWS
- Made back-up plans and optimized servers' performances